free-3gp-video.com 2012-01-06

# Privacy Policy 3gpzone.com

At 3gpZone.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit 3gpZone.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Information Collection and Use**  
Unless the user provides it voluntarily, 3gpZone.com does not collect any personally identifiable information about visitors of the website. Some pages permit visitors to request additional information. Visitors are able to e-mail messages to 3gpZone.com that will contain the user's name and e-mail address, as well as any additional information the user may wish to include in the message. 3gpZone.com uses the information visitors provide about themselves to fulfill those visitors requests. E-mail addresses are used to answer messages received only.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. We use log files to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site.

**Third Party Advertisers**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on 3gpZone.com site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads based on the visit to sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**External Links**  
This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that 3gpZone.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by 3gpZone.com website.

**Security**  
Given the nature of the Internet and the fact that no security system is perfect, 3gpZone.com cannot promise that the information you provide will never be obtained by unauthorized persons. 3gpZone.com does, however, utilize industry-standard practices to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, misuse, alteration and destruction. Such measures include using firewalls and security layers to protect certain sensitive transmissions of information.

By using this site, you signify your assent to the 3gpZone.com Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this site. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Please check back from time to time to ensure that you are aware of these changes. Your continued use of this site will signify your acceptance of these changes.

﻿
